And turned into a puddle of goo.
Now, we can either sit around
and cry over spilt professor...
...or we can rejoice in the knowledge
that a tenured position has just opened up.
I choose to do the latter.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
the whole tenure system is ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)A guaranteed job for life only encourages
the faculty to become complacent.
(Sheldon:)If we really want science to advance...
(Sheldon:)...people should have chips
implanted in their skulls...
(Sheldon:)...that explode
when they say something stupid.
(Raj:)Well, I believe people do their best work
when they feel safe and secure.
(Barry:)If you need my nose,
you'll find it firmly lodged...
...up the rectum of the tenure committee.
You PhDs gonna go suck up like Kripke?
(Leonard:)No. I mean, I'll apply,
but I'm not gonna stoop to playing politics.
(Raj:)Yeah, me neither.
It should be about the work.
(Raj:)And if I can't get tenure,
I'd like to see you or Sheldon get it.
(Sheldon:)Raj, don't dangle false hope
in front of Leonard like that.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, but I think I'm just as qualified
as you are.